Charon Asetoyer Papers, 1985-2008
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. SPEAKING AND WRITING
  - "HIV/AIDS Universal Precaution Practices in Sun Dance Ceremonies" in Journal of Health Education, Nov/Dec 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - "HIV Cultural Competency Within Native American Communities," The Summit on National Guidelines, Planning Committee Meeting [National Advisory Council on HIV Health Disparities]: presentation slides Jun 2005, [see SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS for the digital file of the presentation slides] (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - "Indigenous Women's Health and Rights are...Human Rights" Funders Network on Population, Reproductive Health, and Rights Annual Meeting, Cuernavaca, Mexico: presentation slides, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - "Mother Earth is Not For Sale: The Struggle Never Stops" draft for Ms., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - "Population Control: What's In Store for Indigenous Peoples" 6 Oct 1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Remarks to the Advisory Committee on the Employment of Women in South Dakota, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - "South Dakota's New Murderers," TomPaine.com Commentary, by Lynn Paltrow and Charon Asetoyer, 21 Mar 2006 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - "Toxics-Household, Medical Waste, Landfills, Incinerators and Nuclear Waste Issues and Our Environment: Community Empowerment Methods" workshop, 23 Sep 1992 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
  - [NOTE: Original Audiovisual items are closed, use copies must be made for research use]
  - 13 Radio interviews with Charon Asetoyer [audio cd] 1998-2006 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Interview with Charon Asetoyer conducted by Alana Y. Price [audio cd]26 Jul 2006 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Minnesota Indigenous Language Symposium, Highlights, Producer Lorraine Norrgard, The Grotto Foundation & the Dept of American Indian Studies, College of Liberal Arts, University of Minnesota [dvd] 16-17 Oct 2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "HIV Cultural Competency Within Native American Communities," The Summit on National Guidelines, Planning Committee Meeting [National Advisory Council on HIV Health Disparities]: presentation slides, [cd]Jun 2005, [see SERIES IV. SPEAKING AND WRITING for a printout of the presentation slides] (Box 8, Folder 4)